triviaData = [
        {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "AMC&#039;s &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;, Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were introduced to us in Season 1.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "DragonForce&#039;s &#039;Through the Fire and Flames&#039; is widely considered to be the hardest song in the Guitar Hero series.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "&quot;Elementary, my dear Watson&quot; is a phrase that is never truly said within the Conan Doyle books of Sherlock Holmes.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Cats have whiskers under their legs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The Reckoning&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Norway has a larger land area than Sweden.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Minecraft wasn&rsquo;t the original name to Minecraft.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "&quot;Resident Evil 7&quot; is the first first-person Resident Evil game.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
